<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>mattkorus.com</title><description>The personal website of Matt Korus</description><link>https://your-website-url.com</link><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:30:45 -0800</lastBuildDate><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 13:30:45 -0800</pubDate><ttl>250</ttl><atom:link href="https://your-website-url.com/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://your-website-url.com/posts/December%2017th,%202023</guid><title>Let's see where this leads</title><description>A new project.</description><link>https://your-website-url.com/posts/December%2017th,%202023</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 10:53:00 -0800</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Let's see where this leads</h1><p>December 17th, 2023</p><p>My initial goal here is to create a website using Swift and as much SwiftUI as possible. I only began learning Swift, and really programming at this level, in 2023. So, this will be a learning experience. This is to say that nothing here is going to be a recommendation. I’m going to make a bunch of mistakes, and even when I feel I’m crushing I’m sure many people will feel otherwise.</p><p>Right now I’m going to write into text files and save them locally. I will hopefully advance past this at some point. I have a domain, but no web hosting setup yet. So this will see the light of day later on, if ever.</p><p>Each time I learn something new, or more likely, fail miserably, I’ll do my best to create a new entry here. As of today, what you're reading is all of the progress I've made. None.</p><p>Here’s to the hope of an eventual Swift powered blogging platform,</p><p>-Matt</p>]]></content:encoded></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://your-website-url.com/posts/December%2018th,%202023</guid><title>Initial Progress is Made</title><description>Quicker than anticipated.</description><link>https://your-website-url.com/posts/December%2018th,%202023</link><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 10:53:00 -0800</pubDate><content:encoded><![CDATA[<h1>Initial Progress is Made</h1><p>December 18th, 2023</p><p>Last night, I discovered Publish (https://github.com/JohnSundell/Publish). I've read quite a bit on the Swift by Sundell site, but hadn't realized that a Swift tool was used in making it. It seems this will make my whole journey a lot shorter here.</p><p>I now have a site that I can run locally, so there's a start. Shoutout to Danijela Vrzan for danijelavrzan.com and an easy to follow getting started guide.</p><p>I already own mattkorus.com - I'll have to get this set up over there next.</p><p>-Matt</p>]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>